[{"answer": "No, I'm not.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 26, "question": "You're not that crazy guy anymore?", "qSentId": 25}, {"answer": "Thank you.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 49, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 48}, {"answer": "I've got to say, you look great.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "It's a little cringeable.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 113, "question": "What do you feel about what you just watched there, yourself?", "qSentId": 112}, {"answer": "It's softened a little bit.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 132, "question": "Has your view of addiction and how to deal with it changed in -- in the two years since then?", "qSentId": 131}, {"answer": "No, I'm not.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 139, "question": "You're not -- you're not that crazy guy anymore?", "qSentId": 138}, {"answer": "You could have avoided being fired, probably.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "You know?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "It was -- it was pretty adrenal.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 163, "question": "How hard was it for you, even with all the experience you had, to have your life in this huge goldfish bowl over that period, where everybody was talking about nothing else but Charlie Sheen?", "qSentId": 162}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "I hadn't started yet?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "Yes, the stand you're taking is really -- it's really impressive.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 208, "question": "On the gun thing?", "qSentId": 207}, {"answer": "Well, the last recorded year of 2011 in England and Wales was 39.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 218, "question": "How many -- how many homicides in your country last year with handguns?", "qSentId": 217}, {"answer": "I think the problem that the people face -- well, there's two things.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "Do you understand?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "-- I get why Americans want to defend themselves at home.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "We have a standing army and all that, you know?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "I have, yes.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 248, "question": "Have you ever owned guns yourself?", "qSentId": 247}, {"answer": "I'm OK with it.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "And how do you feel about that?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "I miss shooting.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "But do you -- do you miss having guns around?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "When you see people say that, look, you can't ignore the influence of a violent Hollywood film --", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 259, "question": "But I -- but I didn't -- I didn't carry and I didn't -- I didn't feel like, something that was a -- they were tools for -- for what I was using them for, not for all the negative stuff, you know?", "qSentId": 258}, {"answer": "Yes, I think it can.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 268, "question": "-- influence people?", "qSentId": 267}, {"answer": "I mean, Quentin Tarantino would argue, as he has done about his own films, that he merely reflects what is actually happening in real life.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "I think there's -- there's -- I think more damage can be done with a -- with a show like \"Criminal Minds,\" where like some guy is out there planning his next big serial kill and gets the idea from some of that stuff, where it's just really twisted and evil and hard to what watch, you know?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "I feel very sort of frustrated, like I think a lot of people do, that you can't even have the debate.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "I don't know, I wish -- I wish I had a solution and I -- and I do, and I'm sure you feel the same way, you know?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "Which is why does anyone need an AR-15 military-style weapon anyway?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "Fighting a war.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 295, "question": "Huh?", "qSentId": 294}, {"answer": "I met him once at a party and I'm assuming he was in a bad mood, because he wasn't the friendliest guy in the world.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "What's your view of him?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "Yes, I'm sure people have said that about me from time to time.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 309, "question": "He was rude to you?", "qSentId": 308}, {"answer": "I said, I said, Mr. Armstrong, I'm sorry to bother you.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 312, "question": "What did he say to you?", "qSentId": 311}, {"answer": "That's nice.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 318, "question": "When was this?", "qSentId": 317}, {"answer": "And I said no, it's not nice, ass.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "When was this?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "And that's all he said to you?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "Did he ever shake your hand?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "Again, I don't want to -- I don't want to, you know, tell both sides of the story, because I don't know what he was into that night, or what was going on.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "And then what happened?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "I mean, to me, he's one of the biggest and worst cheats in sporting history, because the number of lives that he adversely affected -- you know, I get all the Livestrong thing.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "And then I just -- I -- I've just been on the sidelines with the rest of us watching the fall from grace, you know?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "I think America is very forgiving if the person hasn't been like you described some of the behavior that that Lance pursued.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "\"Major League.\"", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "Which film was that?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "It made me crazy.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "Did it really?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "Well, it was a disaster --", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "A lot of people talk about Bonds and well, you know, this Hall of Fame thing recently that I think was kind of a bit of a disaster, you know?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "So, I mean, why would you put a cheat into the Hall of Fame?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "HEEN: I'd like to sit down and talk to him and make my own opinion based on an experience with him, not just based on, you know, sideline Monday morning quarterbacking.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "Do you forgive Lance Armstrong then?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "It's a place where you can do whatever you want and nobody bothers you.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "What's a man cave?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "Life imitating -- yes.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "Does it ever get easier?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "I know you did a new movie --", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 445, "question": "Because I have \"Charlie Swan\" coming out also, you know?", "qSentId": 444}, {"answer": "I am.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 453, "question": "You're giving up Charlie completely?", "qSentId": 452}, {"answer": "HEEN: -- I didn't have any children, Charlie.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "In all -- in all senses?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 466, "question": "I think over 90, right?", "qSentId": 465}, {"answer": "It's a lot more fun, yes, because you can make a lot more choices.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 486, "question": "Is it more fun doing these sort of shows sober?", "qSentId": 485}, {"answer": "Not as much as I used to.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "Do you -- do you still party much or?", "qSentId": 490}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 494, "question": "You haven't completely given up?", "qSentId": 493}, {"answer": "ORGAN: But does that really -- I've always wondered if that really makes a difference.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "But, and I think that -- that can slow down the choices that -- that one can make, you know?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "It shouldn't be, but when the -- when the show is run by AA Nazis, then it takes on a different light --", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "If you're playing a womanizing party boy, why would looking hangover be brand damaging?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "I still haven't spoken to him.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "So come on, how -- how do you get on with him these days?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "No, nothing, zero, yes.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 532, "question": "Not a single word?", "qSentId": 531}, {"answer": "I'd have walked right up to him and said, hey, man, you know, good luck with everything.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 537, "question": "What would you have said if you had bumped into him?", "qSentId": 536}, {"answer": "I get -- yes, I just wish that -- that he would acknowledge, at some point, that he had a hand in it.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "Do you harbor resentments toward him?", "qSentId": 549}, {"answer": "There's parts of him I miss -- yes, because when I look back at the -- at the -- at the pilot of \"Two and A Half,\" it was an absolute gem.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 563, "question": "-- do you miss him?", "qSentId": 562}, {"answer": "Just for the record, yes.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "Would you?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 592, "question": "Is this show good with him, do you think?", "qSentId": 591}, {"answer": "I watched it early on.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "Do you ever watch it?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 610, "question": "Do you ever speak to him?", "qSentId": 609}, {"answer": "No, he was -- he was fabulous, yes.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 613, "question": "Was he friendly to you?", "qSentId": 612}, {"answer": "Angus, what does the Bible say about \"Two and A Half Men?\"", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 635, "question": "Are you all completely crack heads (ph) on this show?", "qSentId": 634}, {"answer": "I didn't think it was an act.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 642, "question": "Well, when you -- when you first saw that, what did you think?", "qSentId": 641}, {"answer": "Not even close.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 646, "question": "Had he shown any signs of this kind of extreme religious philosophy or?", "qSentId": 645}, {"answer": "But when he went off like this, he then regretted it and said he wished he hadn't.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 652, "question": "It was never -- religion was never -- I think there was one episode about it, but, you know, it wasn't like a water cooler topic or anything, you know?", "qSentId": 651}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 659, "question": "You know what I'm saying?", "qSentId": 658}, {"answer": "Good question.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 674, "question": "So, Charlie, why did you give Lindsay Lohan $100,000?", "qSentId": 673}, {"answer": "No, no, no.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 679, "question": "Did you get it back?", "qSentId": 678}, {"answer": "Eventually.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 693, "question": "Was she grateful?", "qSentId": 692}, {"answer": "Eventually, yes.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 696, "question": "Eventually?", "qSentId": 695}, {"answer": "She is, in many ways, someone who has gone through a not dissimilar path from you.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 701, "question": "She's a busy young lady, you know?", "qSentId": 700}, {"answer": "If -- the only thing that I was sad about -- if she had asked me questions about some of my own stuff, I would have gladly given her advice, but she didn't.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 705, "question": "Or is it, in the end, the look in the mirror and work it out for yourself?", "qSentId": 704}, {"answer": "He didn't.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 737, "question": "When you react in the way that you do, which was pretty aggressively against what he said, how did he respond to that?", "qSentId": 736}, {"answer": "Oh, hell yes.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 742, "question": "And did that happen?", "qSentId": 741}, {"answer": "There was a moment we had where -- I think the tour ended.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 744, "question": "How did that happen?", "qSentId": 743}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 761, "question": "You speak to him much now?", "qSentId": 760}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 769, "question": "Does he know how possibly influential he's been on your recovery?", "qSentId": 768}, {"answer": "It does It does.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 772, "question": "Which must makes him very proud?", "qSentId": 771}, {"answer": "They handle it differently.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 781, "question": "Or is everyone different?", "qSentId": 780}, {"answer": "But it may save your life.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 809, "question": "You're like, now what?", "qSentId": 808}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 816, "question": "Is that always the demon on your shoulder?", "qSentId": 815}, {"answer": "Because I thought a lot of it was very entertaining, if I'm honest with you.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 823, "question": "I think it just -- again, things just sort of got ahead of themselves and you start playing catch-up, trying to put the blocks back together, you know?", "qSentId": 822}, {"answer": "It was in Detroit, opening night.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 838, "question": "Did you have a moment where you suddenly went, I'm not doing this anymore, or certainly not at the level I have been doing it?", "qSentId": 837}, {"answer": "I look at you now and I see somebody not unrecognizable from two years ago, but certainly a very different Charlie Sheen.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 853, "question": "And I did, against all odds, you know?", "qSentId": 852}, {"answer": "Perfect link to what the next segment --", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 866, "question": "Not bad, right?", "qSentId": 865}, {"answer": "It's about women.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 868, "question": "Is it about horses?", "qSentId": 867}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 891, "question": "You enjoyed making it?", "qSentId": 890}, {"answer": "With a girlfriend.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 896, "question": "Where are you at the moment with women?", "qSentId": 895}, {"answer": "No, just a girlfriend.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 898, "question": "A goddess?", "qSentId": 897}, {"answer": "They went their separate ways.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 900, "question": "What happened to the goddesses?", "qSentId": 899}, {"answer": "It gets complicated, yes, yes.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 904, "question": "Every man's dream or does it get complicated?", "qSentId": 903}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 917, "question": "She's an adult entertainer?", "qSentId": 916}, {"answer": "Yes, a couple years.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 933, "question": "She's given it up?", "qSentId": 932}, {"answer": "Yes, I am.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 939, "question": "Are you in love with her?", "qSentId": 938}, {"answer": "I thought I was.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 946, "question": "Were you properly in love each time?", "qSentId": 945}, {"answer": "She's 28.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 963, "question": "ORGAN: She's now in her late 20s, your daughter, right?", "qSentId": 962}, {"answer": "They're pretty good.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 979, "question": "And how are your kids, your twin boys?", "qSentId": 978}, {"answer": "Sorry.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 987, "question": "Do you see much of the boys?", "qSentId": 986}, {"answer": "I have five.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 993, "question": "How many kids?", "qSentId": 992}, {"answer": "They're becoming friends, absolutely.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 997, "question": "Are they all friends with each other, the kids?", "qSentId": 996}, {"answer": "To a degree, yes.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 1000, "question": "When you see the influence and impact your father had on you, do you understand more of the power of you as a father to be a role model to you kids?", "qSentId": 999}, {"answer": "I believe that I am, yes.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 1002, "question": "Are you ready for that?", "qSentId": 1001}, {"answer": "Live with the truth.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 1006, "question": "What would be the number one bit of advice you give one of your sons, perhaps?", "qSentId": 1005}, {"answer": "He might want to tone it down just a little bit.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 1064, "question": "How would you go on if he brought that particular style to the Oscars?", "qSentId": 1063}, {"answer": "He was superb.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 1072, "question": "He was great at the roast, wasn't he?", "qSentId": 1071}, {"answer": "It was fantastic.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 1091, "question": "I thought it was pretty good, right?", "qSentId": 1090}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 1094, "question": "Did any of it hurt you?", "qSentId": 1093}, {"answer": "Not too many.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 1102, "question": "Have you seen many movies?", "qSentId": 1101}, {"answer": "When I was in Atlanta, I went and saw \"Safe House\" a few months ago.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 1104, "question": "Do you ever actually go and buy a ticket and go to a movie theater?", "qSentId": 1103}, {"answer": "HEEN: They usually wait until the film is over to talk to me, which is polite.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 1111, "question": "How do they react?", "qSentId": 1110}, {"answer": "I'm a baseball player in my heart.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 1114, "question": "Are you, at your heart, a movie star, do you think?", "qSentId": 1113}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 1120, "question": "That would have been the dream for you?", "qSentId": 1119}, {"answer": "Absolutely, at the drop of a hat.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 1128, "question": "Would you really?", "qSentId": 1127}, {"answer": "Because he did \"Fast Times\" and \"Dead Men Walking.\"", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 1138, "question": "Why is he so good?", "qSentId": 1137}, {"answer": "Wow.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 1148, "question": "ORGAN: Who is the best actress?", "qSentId": 1147}, {"answer": "Just for sheer amount of amazing --", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 1151, "question": "You'd have to almost -- you'd have to go with Streep I think, you know?", "qSentId": 1150}, {"answer": "I will, indeed.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 1159, "question": "Will you be watching the Oscars?", "qSentId": 1158}, {"answer": "Yes, he's number two.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 1170, "question": "Daniel Day-Lewis?", "qSentId": 1169}, {"answer": "Today I am with you.", "docId": "130126pmt", "aSentId": 1175, "question": "Are you still winning, Charlie?", "qSentId": 1174}]